

■ sam@macalu.so | 🏔 macalu.so | 🖸 oonis | 🛅 oonis

# Summary\_

Current member and back-end developer at Better Games LLC. 6+ years experience specializing in security, data mining and recognition, and backend development for both web and native applications. Interested in problem solving, designing and implementing applications, and cyber security.

# **Work Experience**

## Michigan State University School of Planning, Design and Construction

East Lansing

DEVELOPER February 2019 - Present

• Utilize ArcGIS for displaying housing data statistics on a PHP website.

# **Better Games LLC**

TECHNICAL ASSISTANT

FOLINDER November 2018 - Present

- · Designed and implemented the C# backend as well as the netcode used to communicate with Steam
- · Handled communication with publishers as well as documentation for forming the company

### Michigan State University Institute for Cyber-Enabled Research

East Lansing

July 2017 - February 2019

- · Wrote build scripts and maintained packages for the HPCC.
- · Worked on upgrading systems to a new node cluster.

### Michigan State University RS&GIS

East Lansing

WEB DEVELOPER November 2015 - March 2017

- Developed the admissions portal and course registration for the MSU college of Social Work.
- Developed and maintained the course registration website for the MSU School of Human Resources and Labor Relations.

### Michigan State University Plant Research Laboratory

East Lansing

RESEARCH ASSISTANT December 2012 - January 2015

Worked on several papers and projects with faculty including: Visual Phenomics, image recognition and processing for calculating photosynthetic data of plants and PhenoMath, analyze the output from Visual Phenomics, running pattern recognition and outlier detection algorithms to determine interesting data-points.

# Public Projects \_\_\_\_\_

#### **Puttin' Around**

ONLINE MULTIPLAYER MINI GOLF GAME WRITTEN IN C-SHARP RUNNING OFF OF THE UNITY ENGINE. DISTRIBUTED VIA STEAM, AND RUN OFF OF DEDICATED SERVERS.

2019

## **MSU Social Work Undergraduate Application system**

EASY APPLICATION FOR MSU STUDENTS TO APPLY TO THE SCHOOL OF SOCIAL WORK. ADMINISTRATION PORTAL NOT PUBLICLY AVALIABLE. WRITTEN IN PHP WITH A MYSQL DATABASE.

2017

## MSU School of Human Resources and Labor Relations Course Registration

EASY WEB REGISTRATION FOR THE MSU SCHOOL OF HRLR, WRITTEN IN PHP WITH A MYSQL BACKEND.

2017

### FΔT

A NODE. JS WEBSITE TO PARSE AND COMBINE DINING MENUS FOR VARIOUS SOURCES.

2017

# Education

COMPUTER SCIENCE

**Michigan State University** 

East Lansing

2011 - 2018

- Placed 4th at the ACM ICPC 2012.
- Placed 3rd at MHacks 1.

Skills\_

**Languages** C, C++, C#, Coq, Go, Java, Javascript, PHP, Python, Rust, SQL

**Interests** Cyber Security, Penetration Testing, Machine Learning, Pattern Recognition